in this video we are going to show you
在本视频中，我们将向您展示
how to connect your java applications to
如何将Java应用程序连接到
autonomous transaction processing my
自主交易处理
name is Nabil ascender Appa
名字是Nabil Ascender Appa
I'm the principal product manager for
我是的首席产品经理
Oracle JDBC and UCP let's begin with
让我们从Oracle JDBC和UCP开始
prerequisites the first prerequisite is
先决条件第一个先决条件是
to provision the autonomous transaction
提供自主交易
processing sign in with your cloud
处理您的云登录
credentials at cloud.oracle.com and
cloud.oracle.com上的凭证和
create an EDP database by filling in few
通过填写几个来创建EDP数据库
details
细节
the second prerequisite is to download
第二个前提条件是下载
the client credentials from service
服务中的客户端凭据
console after your ATP is created click
创建ATP之后，请单击控制台
on service console and login as admin
在服务控制台上并以管理员身份登录
user click on download client
用户点击下载客户端
credentials to download the walnut zip
下载核桃zip的凭据
file by entering the wallet password
通过输入钱包密码来归档文件
make sure to save this to a secure
确保将其保存到安全
location where only authorized people
只有授权人员的位置
have access to it the zip file contains
有权访问的zip文件包含
all the files listed here the third
这里列出的所有文件第三
prerequisite is to install the latest
前提是要安装最新的
JDK make sure to have JDK 10 RJD k9r JDK
JDK确保拥有JDK 10 RJD k9r JDK
8 update 162 also download the latest
8更新162也下载了最新的
18.3 JDBC driver and UCP along with the
18.3 JDBC驱动程序和UCP以及
JDBC driver and UCP you also need Oracle
JDBC驱动程序和UCP您还需要Oracle
PKI dot jar an esthetic underscore cold
PKI点罐感性强调
jar and OS ET underscore Sirdar jar if
jar和OS ET下划线Sirdar jar如果
you are using Oracle wallets there are
您正在使用Oracle钱包
two ways to connect to ATP
两种连接ATP的方法
one using Java key stores and a second
一个使用Java密钥存储区，另一个
using Oracle wallets I will walk you
使用Oracle钱包，我会带你走
through the code samples to connect to
通过代码示例连接到
ATP using both these approaches I have
使用这两种方法的ATP
downloaded UCP sample dot Java from
从以下位置下载了UCP样本点Java
github the first step is to update the
github的第一步是更新
database URL username and password
数据库URL用户名和密码
pointing to the ADP database that you
指向您的ADP数据库
have created also use TNS Elyas from DNS
从DNS创建了也使用TNS Elyas
name start aura DNS name start aura can
名称启动光环DNS名称启动光环可以
be found from the client credential zip
从客户端凭证zip中找到
file that you download from your cloud
您从云下载的文件
account in this sample we are using JDBC
此示例中的帐户，我们正在使用JDBC
test underscore medium the DNS admin
测试下划线中的DNS管理员
should be pointing to the location where
应该指向的位置
you have unzipped the client credentials
您已解压缩客户端凭据
note that
注意
DNS admin can be a set as part of the
DNS管理员可以作为一组
database URL and this is a feature which
数据库URL，这是一个功能
was introduced in 18.3 if you are using
如果您使用的是18.3
the JDBC driver that is lower than 18.3
低于18.3的JDBC驱动程序
then you can set cleaners admin either
然后您可以设置清洁剂管理员
as a system property or as a connection
作为系统属性或连接
property another important file that you
拥有另一个重要文件
need to know is ODB CDOT properties file
需要知道的是ODB CDOT属性文件
and this is the file that is also part
这也是该文件的一部分
of the the client credential zip file
客户端凭证zip文件
and here you can add Oracle Wallet
在这里您可以添加Oracle Wallet
related and also JK's related connection
相关以及JK的相关连接
properties and this is also a new
属性，这也是一个新的
feature that was introduced in 18.3 now
现在在18.3中引入的功能
let's go back to the sample let's see
让我们回到示例，让我们看看
what the sample does we are going to
我们将要采样什么
create a table customer table and insert
创建表客户表并插入
two records into this table and update
此表中有两个记录并进行更新
one of the record and then we will show
记录之一，然后我们将显示
the two records from the table after
表中的两个记录之后
everything is done we are going to clean
一切都完成了，我们要清理
up and drop the table
上下桌子
let's see these code samples in action
让我们来看一下这些代码示例
let's see how to use Java keystore to
让我们看看如何使用Java密钥库来
connect to a TPM I have created a folder
连接到TPM我已经创建了一个文件夹
ATP testing and placed all the files you
ATP测试并放置所有文件
can see you see P sample dot Java and
可以看到您看到P个样本点Java和
the folder Lib contains the JDBC driver
Lib文件夹包含JDBC驱动程序
and you see P dot jar from 18.3 you can
您会看到从18.3开始的P点罐
see that the JDBC driver is from 18.3 I
看到JDBC驱动程序来自18.3 I
have unzipped the wallet credentials to
已将钱包凭证解压缩到
the folder wallet underscore JDBC test
文件夹钱包强调JDBC测试
you can see all JDBC dot properties file
您可以看到所有JDBC点属性文件
and also J key is an Oracle wallet
而且J键是Oracle钱包
related files as part of connecting to
相关文件作为连接到的一部分
ATP using kks you need to edit or JDBC
ATP使用kks需要编辑或JDBC
dot properties file make sure you add
点属性文件确保您添加
the jks related connection properties to
与jks相关的连接属性
this file and also the clustered
该文件以及集群
password and the keystore password
密码和密钥库密码
should be updated to the password that
应该更新为
you used while downloading the client
您在下载客户端时使用的
credentials zip file also make sure you
凭证zip文件还可以确保您
comment the Oracle wallet related
评论与Oracle钱包相关的
connection property and these are the
连接属性，这些是
changes that we need to connect or
我们需要连接的更改或
connect to ATP using gks let's compile
使用gks连接到ATP，让我们进行编译
the Java code let's run the Java sample
Java代码让我们运行Java示例
you can see that we successfully
您可以看到我们成功
connected to ATP using jks now let's use
现在使用jks连接到ATP
Oracle wallets to connect to ATP I'm
Oracle钱包可以连接到ATP
using UCP sample dot java and in the lib
使用UCP示例点java和lib中
directory I have added oracle pkg our
目录我已经添加了oracle pkg
host Atlantis cursor dodge our an OST T
主机亚特兰蒂斯游标闪避我们的OST T
and is called cold archer in addition to
除了被称为冷弓箭手
the JDBC driver and you zippe targe are
JDBC驱动程序和zippe目标是
these three additional jars are required
这三个额外的罐子是必需的
while connecting using Oracle wallets
使用Oracle钱包进行连接时
wallet underscore JDBC test has all the
钱包下划线JDBC测试具有所有
client residential files to unzip open
客户端住宅文件解压缩打开
or JDBC third properties file make sure
或JDBC第三个属性文件，请确保
that you have the wallet related
你有钱包相关
connection property uncommented now
连接属性现在未注释
let's compile the code sample let's run
让我们编译代码示例，让我们运行
the code sample you can see that we
代码示例，您可以看到我们
successfully connected to ATP using
使用以下命令成功连接到ATP
Oracle wallets thank you for watching
甲骨文钱包感谢您的观看
the video
该视频